<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><docs><p0><title>UK: FOCUS - Zeneca profits surge but shares slip.</title><detail>British drugs and chemicals company Zeneca Group PlcL on Thursday announced first-half profits well above expectations, but shares still eased back as investors focused instead on the cost of launching new drugs later this year.Pre-tax profits jumped 9.7 percent to 669 million pounds ($1.1 billion) from 610 million, well above analysts' median forecasts of 649 million pounds.The performance outshone both its main British rivals, SmithKline Beecham Plc and Glaxo Wellcome Plc.Zeneca said its policy of currency hedging had protected profits from the worst excesses of sterling's advance over the past year. But the strong pound still wiped 300 million pounds off sales, which fell six percent to 2.75 billion pounds, and 90 million pounds off operating profits.Ignoring exchange rate differences, pre-tax profit was up 22 percent and sales advanced 10 percent.Despite the bullish performance, shares in Zeneca slipped back by up to 51-1/2 pence during the morning as investors reacted nervously to the company's warnings of a &amp;quot;substantial&amp;quot; rise in launch costs in the second part of the year. By late morning the stock was down 21-1/2 pence at 20.25 stg.&amp;quot;There will be substantial new product launch costs to come in the second half of the year,&amp;quot; chief executive David Barnes told Reuters. He predicted full-year profit margins at the group, which rose sharply to 24 percent from 21.2 percent in the first half, would be between two and 2.5 percentage points lower for the full-year, in line with Zeneca's historic performance.Describing the results as &amp;quot;cracking good,&amp;quot; Barnes said &amp;quot;most pleasing to me is the improvement in the margin...and that is after soaking up the adverse currency hit. That is a very good set of figures and improvements have come across all three sectors - pharmaceuticals, agrochemicals and specialities.&amp;quot;Barnes said the gain was a result of restructuring undertaken last year, notably reorganisation of the seeds business and disposal of textile colours, and an improvement in the mix of products, with more profitable new products being introduced.The third factor was the shifting of some launch costs anticipated in the first half of the year to the second half, when Zeneca hopes to launch migraine drug Zomig in the U.S, asthma pill Accolate in Europe and schizophrenia treatment Seroquel on both sides of the Atlantic.BZW analyst Steve Plag, who had forecast pre-tax profit of 645 million pounds, said &amp;quot;overall we were pretty pleased with the results.&amp;quot;&amp;quot;These were clearly a set of figures which were better than the market anticipated, but with the caveat of substantial launch costs to come in the second half,&amp;quot; he added. ($ = 0.624 British Pounds)</detail><filename>785734newsML.xml</filename></p0><p1><title>GERMANY: FOCUS - MAN profit up despite tough markets.</title><detail>Overcoming difficult markets in its main business areas, German truck and engineering group MAN AG AG reported on Tuesday a 21 percent increase in net profit to 330 million marks ($223.8 million) in the 1995/96 business year.MAN, whose fortunes are closely tied to broad economic trends, said it expected another good year in 1996/97.&amp;quot;The high, if not evenly distributed level of orders in hand ... as well as continued efforts to improve our competitive position on the product and cost side allow the MAN group to be confident for 1996/1997,&amp;quot; MAN said in a statement.The Munich-based group reported sales for the 1995/96 business year ending June 30 of 20.27 billion marks, up from 18.60 billion marks in the year-earlier period.Group net profit rose to 330 million marks from 272 million marks, prompting MAN to raise its dividend payout to 12 marks per share from 9.50 marks in the 1994/95 business year.&amp;quot;Business only livened up in the last quarter,&amp;quot; MAN said. The group noted, however, that the recovery had since also spread to the German market.The group added that it should remain successful in the current year unless the capital goods industry weakened again, after showing initial recovery tendencies.Stock traders said the figures were as good as could have been hoped for and pushed MAN's share price up 16.70 marks to 369.50 in afternoon trade.The company's truck making unit, MAN Nutzfahrzeuge AG, facing a weak west European market, still managed to see sales climb 10 percent to just under eight billion marks and pre-tax profits climb 50 million marks to 260 million marks.Although the market for heavy trucks in western Europe was sharply lower, the division saw unit sales of trucks over six tonnes climb three percent.The global truck industry suffered last year with weak economic growth in many major regions giving truck companies little reason to expand their fleets.MAN will face increased competition from rival Mercedes-Benz AG next year when the Stuttgart-based company introduces a new line of heavy trucks.MAN's printing machine company, MAN Roland Druckmaschinen, slashed losses to 80 million marks in 1995/96 from 146 million marks the year before.MAN said the unit remained in the loss column because of costs associated with the introduction of a new generation sheet paper printers.Indeed, sales climbed 18 percent in 1995/96 from the year before to 2.4 billion marks.The company said the remaining loss will be reduced by cost cutting.MAN Roland has incoming orders of 2.2 billion marks, down 6.6 percent from the same period.The company said results at its MAN B&amp;amp;W Diesel motor division was especially encouraging, benefitting from a boom in ship production.($1=1.4747 Mark)</detail><filename>17550newsML.xml</filename></p1><p2><title>UK: Sainsbury still struggles vs Tesco.</title><detail>British supermarket retailer J. Sainsbury Plc has been struggling for well over a year to regain the leading position which it lost to arch-rival Tesco in 1995 but has failed to boost sales convincingly.The following is a brief history of the &amp;quot;Store Wars&amp;quot; between Britain's supermarket giants:- February 1995: Tesco launches ClubCard loyalty card. - September 1995: Tesco noses ahead of Sainsbury in market share, pushing into the lead position.- October 1995: Sainsbury announces appointment of Kevin McCarten, previously at Woolworths discount chain, as marketing director.- January 1996: Sainsbury bows to market pressure and announces that chairman and chief executive roles will be split. David Sainsbury continues as chairman but two chief executives to be appointed, with Tom Vyner taking post in supermarkets division.Dino Adriano lined up to replace Vyner at end-1997.- January 26: Sainsbury warns that year profits will be below expectations.- March 1996: Sainsbury cuts beef prices as impact of scares over Bovine Spongiform Encephalopathy (BSE) or &amp;quot;mad cow&amp;quot; disease hit sales.- May 8: Sainsbury announces first fall in profits for 22 years as annual pretax figure slides to 712 million pounds from 809 million pounds.- May 8: David Bremner joins as chief executive of Sainsbury's Homebase and U.S. businesses.- June 1996: Tesco adds ClubCard Plus interest-paying card to its loyalty stable.- June 1996: Sainsbury pushed into launching loyalty card in U-turn from earlier policy.- September 23: Buys 12 stores in the U.S. from Royal Ahold.- September 1996: Around 30 million shares from institutional investors placed.- October 1996: Sainsbury's Bank, joint venture with Bank of Scotland, launched. Sainsbury is first of big four supermarkets to move into banking with project likely to be up and running in first quarter of 1997.- October 1996: Sainsbury's half year pretax profits slip to 393 million pounds versus 456 million pounds and full year profit forecasts cut to 710-725 million pounds.- October 1996: Dino Adriano's takeover from Tom Vyner brought forward to March 1997.- January 1997: Homebase do-it-yourself chain announces it will offer insurance products in partnership with brokers Willis Corroon.- January 1997: Latest market share figures show Sainsbury at 20.1 percent, still behind Tesco with 23.2 percent.- January 1997: Sainsbury says same store sales grow 4.4 percent over Christmas and warns that this year's profits will be around 640-650 million pounds, a further slide and well below previous expectations of just over 700 million pounds.-- London Newsroom +44 171 542 7717</detail><filename>331697newsML.xml</filename></p2><p3><title>USA: Movie Gallery sees Q1 EPS range $0.14-$0.17.</title><detail>Movie Gallery Inc said Tuesday it expects earnings per share for the first quarter of 1997, ended April 6, 1997, to range from $0.14 to $0.17 per share, which it said is below average analyst expectations of $0.25 per share.The company said it believes earnings per share will differ from analyst expectations primarily as a result of lower-than-expected revenues. The revenue shortfall is largely the result of a significant level of competitive openings over the past year in the Company's more urban locations, an abnormally mild winter across the majority of the Company's store base, which is located in the southeast and a higher-than-expected level of product sales relative to rental revenue.Same store revenues for the second quarter are anticipated to be down approximately 5.5 percent from the same quarter of the prior year.  Movie Gallery will announce results of its first quarter on May 14, 1997.</detail><filename>528871newsML.xml</filename></p3><p4><title>UK: Treasuries stumble in London, long end suffers most.</title><detail>U.S. Treasuries weakened in London trade on Thursday, led lower by the long end of the curve, but traders and analysts said many players were trying to stay out of the fray in the run-up to payroll data on Friday.Paul Donovan, senior economist at UBS in London, said it was not so much that the market was nervous as that people were avoiding taking positions.&amp;quot;The impression we get certainly among European bond investors in the U.S. is that there is uncertainty about whether the Fed hike is a one-off or part of a series,&amp;quot; he said. &amp;quot;People are sitting on cash positions, short duration positions.&amp;quot;The U.S. long bond at 1006 GMT was at 94-08/32, yielding 7.08 percent, compared with 95-12 bid at the Tokyo close and 94-14 bid in New York on Wednesday.The 10-year T-note was at 95-15 to yield 6.89 percent, off from Tokyo's 95-19 and New York's 95-20. At the short end, two year paper fell to 99-22, for a 6.42 percent yield, from 99-23 in Tokyo and New York.&amp;quot;We've had a bit of a panicky selloff,&amp;quot; said a dealer at a Japanese bank in London. &amp;quot;It's not really a story. They're just softer in sympathy with European markets.&amp;quot;He said the 10-year area seemed to be hardest hit.The trader said in net terms the market appeared generally short going into the U.S. payroll numbers, but he added, &amp;quot;Everybody's a lurking seller at the end of day.&amp;quot;March payrolls, according to a Reuters survey of economists, are forecast to rise 182,000.For Thursday's session, the market was looking ahead to weekly jobless claims at 1330 GMT but analysts said these figures would have limited impact ahead of Friday's report. Claims were forecast at 310,000 in the latest week, unchanged from the prior week.In the futures market, June T-bonds in automted trade were at 107-14, off 4/32 from the Chicago close.-- Adam Cox, International Bonds Unit +44 171 542 6784</detail><filename>485599newsML.xml</filename></p4><p5><title>USA: U.S. tax protester jailed for 36 years for IRS bomb.</title><detail>A tax protester was sentenced to 36 years in prison on Thursday for trying to blow up the U.S. Internal Revenue Service building in Reno.Joseph Bailie, 42, was found guilty in June of three charges in connection with the failed attack on the tax agency last December.The 100-pound (45 kg) fertiliser and fuel oil bomb was found in the car park of the IRS building in Reno. Its three-foot (one-metre) long fuse had burned out and it did not explode.Passing sentence, U.S. District Judge Howard McKibben said Bailie was guilty of &amp;quot;lawless and wanton conduct&amp;quot; with what he called substantial potential for causing serious harm to people and property.Bailie, who had been convicted of conspiracy, the attempted destruction of a government building and the use of an explosive device in the commission of a crime, was also ordered to make restitution to the IRS of $141,000.The Reno bomb was made of similar materials to the one that blew up the federal building in Oklahoma City last year and killed 168 people.</detail><filename>127631newsML.xml</filename></p5><p6><title>GERMANY: Lufthansa Cargo says urgent need for modernisation.</title><detail>Lufthansa Cargo AG needs to modernise itself urgently if it is to return to profit and secure its market leadership, a senior official said.Stefan Lauer, the new Lufthansa Cargo board member responsible for sales and marketing worldwide, said the Deutsche Lufthansa cargo unit was still doing business in the same way as 15 to 20 years ago.In a interview with Lufthansa staff newspaper &amp;quot;Lufthanseat&amp;quot;, Lauer said: &amp;quot;Cargo has for too long taken delight in sheer size and notching up new records.&amp;quot;&amp;quot;There is an urgent need for modernisation and Lufthansa Cargo is lagging behind developments despite its claim to be leading the market,&amp;quot; he admitted.Referring to last year's loss of 59.8 million marks against a 1995 profit of 20.4 million marks, Lauer, who was in passenger operations until this January, said: &amp;quot;For years we had put off dealing with flaws in our operations and they finally caught up with us.Lufthansa Cargo had now launched a &amp;quot;Direction 2000&amp;quot; programme of cost management, modernisation of sales and operations and a strategic re-positioning.&amp;quot;We need a fundamental change of mentality in marketing and sales. We must change from a fleet with a sales office to a marketing operation offering transport services,&amp;quot; Lauer said.This meant active market research, sales and marketing instead of simply waiting for freight inquiries to come, he explained.Closer partnership with forwarders, who generated 95 percent of Lufthansa Cargo revenue, was essential to turn the airline into &amp;quot;an integrator for general cargo&amp;quot;, Lauer stressed.The airline was also building up a global network with other carriers to link the world's economic regions.&amp;quot;That can, but need not, be the partners with which our passenger services are already cooperating. The talks are very promising,&amp;quot; he said.Lufthansa Cargo already has close cargo links for Europe-Asia with Thai Airways International, Singapore Airlines, Cathay Pacific, Korean Air Lines and Japan Air Lines.It largely serves North Atlantic destinations alone, however, although a partnership with United Airlines is now being built up.Other cargo partners include Varig, South African Airways while a close cooperation is planned with SAS Cargo.</detail><filename>573260newsML.xml</filename></p6><p7><title>USA: U.S. new-home sales soar, forecasting gauge rises.</title><detail>Sales of new homes soared to an 11-year high in January, the Commerce Department said on Tuesday in a report that surprised markets by suggesting a housing boom might not be leveling off as anticipated.The department said sales jumped 8.6 percent to a seasonally adjusted annual rate of 870,000 units -- the highest rate since 880,000 in March 1986 -- after a revised 0.5 percent rise in December.Using a new computerized method for gathering sales data that it said may impart some &amp;quot;upward bias&amp;quot; in the figures, the Commerce Department said January sales were a whopping 19.7 percent above the 727,000-unit level reported a year earlier in January 1996.Separately, the Conference Board in New York said its index of leading indicators climbed 0.3 percent in January -- its best monthly gain in eight months -- after a slight 0.1 percent increase in December.Six of 10 measures in the index were stronger than in December, pointing to economic strength in coming months.Analysts were wary about interpreting the home-sales report, partly since the Commerce Department gave no advance notice and scant explanation for its change in methods. It said it was taking steps to &amp;quot;dampen monthly fluctuations&amp;quot; in the report.Bond prices initially dipped before recovering, since Wall Street economists had expected a drop in new-home sales during January instead of a sudden acceleration.&amp;quot;It's a strange report,&amp;quot; said economist David Lereah of the Mortgage Bankers' Association. &amp;quot;Even though it looks like a huge surge in January, perhaps they've just taken us to a new level based on better information.&amp;quot;Everett Ehrlich, Commerce Undersecretary for Economic Affairs, said in a telephone interview the department was sending interviewers with laptop computers to gather information instead of pencil and paper to get more and faster responses from local governments and realtors about sales.&amp;quot;We are very confident that home-sales rose in January and that they rose sizeably,&amp;quot; Ehrlich said.The pickup in January sales came despite higher mortgage rates, but analysts said there were ample other reasons that new homes were bought.&amp;quot;We've seen very healthy growth in jobs, real income and stock prices so consumers have high confidence,&amp;quot; said Sun Won Sohn, an economist with Norwest Corp. in Minneapolis.&amp;quot;Most economists have been saying that housing has topped and should be softening, but home sales have not shown any signs of that,&amp;quot; Sohn noted.Sales of not only new but existing homes were up at the beginning of 1997.Last week, the National Association of Realtors said sales of existing, or used, homes rose 2.1 percent in January to a seasonally adjusted annual rate of 3.94 million.The rise in new-home sales during January was heavily concentrated in the Northeast, where sales jumped 63.4 percent to 134,000 a year -- the highest since 152,000 in November 1987.The only other region where sales rose during January was the South, where they were up 11.9 percent to 403,000 -- the highest since 440,000 in December 1983.By contrast, sales fell 10.3 percent from December levels in the Midwest to 140,000 a year, while in the West they dropped 5.9 percent to 192,000.Previously, the department said December sales had fallen 1 percent to an annual rate of 783,000. But it revised that to show a 0.5 percent gain to a much higher level of 801,000.The Federal Home Loan Mortgage Corp., or Freddie Mac, said rates for a 30-year mortgage averaged 7.82 percent in January, up from 7.60 percent in December and 7.03 percent in January 1996.</detail><filename>418648newsML.xml</filename></p7><p8><title>TURKEY: Turkey party gives Ciller approval to seek polls.</title><detail>The conservative party in Turkey's coalition government cleared the way on Thursday for its leader Tansu Ciller to request early elections in bargaining with Islamist Prime Minister Necmettin Erbakan, Anatolian news agency said.&amp;quot;We gave her the authority for early elections,&amp;quot; it quoted True Path Party leading member Ali Osman Sonmez as saying.Ciller, the deputy prime minister, has asked Erbakan to make her prime minister in a caretaker government that would take the country to the polls.The alliance has been losing deputies in a row with the secularist army over Islamist activism and is close to becoming a minority administration.Turkish television said the parties had agreed on Ciller taking over the premiership in July and going to elections in October, but there was no independent confirmation.The partners are to swop jobs next year under a power-sharing deal that established their alliance last June. But Ciller says she can ward off army pressure on the government better if she takes the top job sooner.&amp;quot;An election can be held by March, 1998 at the latest once the population count and ballot boxes have been prepared,&amp;quot; Sonmez was quoted as saying.A member of the True Path Party's executive council who declined to be named told Reuters that the Welfare Party (RP) favoured handing over the premiership soon. &amp;quot;The RP looks favourably on handing over the prime minister's job. The handover will take place soon.&amp;quot;A late bid to save the government from collapsing ran into trouble at a three-way meeting of party leaders on Wednesday.Right-wing party leader Muhsin Yazicioglu said after the talks that he was reluctant to prop up the coalition until the alliance partners reached accord on the government's future.Yazicioglu said Erbakan, Turkey's first Islamist leader, had so far rejected a call by Ciller to make her prime minister until elections in spring 1998, two years before they are due.&amp;quot;Ciller states that an early election atmosphere has been formed in Turkey. As for Erbakan, he says the government can continue until the year 2000,&amp;quot; Yazicioglu said.Reports of discussions on early elections caused the Istanbul share market to fall sharply on Thursday in near-panic selling. At one stage the IMKB National-100 index was down 4.1 percent but it recovered later to close 2.3 percent down from Wednesday's close.</detail><filename>624266newsML.xml</filename></p8><p9><title>USA: Oscar-winning clay figures missing in N.Y..</title><detail>The violent weather that lashed the U.S. Northeast on Saturday may have claimed two more victims -- Wallace and Gromit, the stars of last year's Oscar-winning short, &amp;quot;A Close Shave.&amp;quot;The two were last seen on Saturday in their travel case, along with their motorcycle and sidecar, in the back of a New York City taxi cab after their creator, Nick Park, arrived for a publicity tour.A porter at Park's hotel failed to see the case in the cab's trunk, and the driver drove away with the two nine-inch (22 cms) plasticine figures held captive and Park chasing the car down the Manhattan street. But to no avail.Police said on Sunday that the loss had been reported but that so far no one had contacted them regarding the duo's whereabouts. Park was not at his hotel on Sunday evening and was possibly out searching the canyons of midtown Manhattan for his lost progeny.He said in media reports the figures were probably worth over $10,000, &amp;quot;but to us they're priceless.&amp;quot;Should Wallace and Gromit be located alive and unharmed, they will likely go on to make other films following the success of such hit short films as &amp;quot;The Wrong Trousers,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;A Grand Day Out,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;A Close Shave,&amp;quot; which won the Oscar this year for Best Animated Short Film.The Northeast was buffeted over the weekend with wind gusts of up to 65 mph (100 kph) and as much as six inches of rain.</detail><filename>131565newsML.xml</filename></p9></docs>