<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><docs><pp><title>USA: NOTICE OF SALE - Three Village CSD, N.Y.</title><detail>SUMMARY NOTICE OF SALE				  $2,177,000		 Three Village Central School District		     of Brookhaven and Smithtown,		  In the County of Suffolk, New York		   School District Serial Bonds-1997		     (callable) (book-entry only)	 SALE: 11:00 o'clock AM Wednesday, August 27, 1997at Hawkins, Delafield &amp;amp;Wood, 67 Wall Street, New York, New				     York  Bonds dated August 15, 1997,   interest December 15, 1997,and semiannually thereafter  on June 15  and December 15  in  each  year   to   maturity.  Bonds   mature   in   principalinstallments on June 15 as follows:$127,000 in the year 1999 $175,000 in the year 2006*$150,000 in the year 2000 $175,000 in the year 2007*$150,000 in the year 2001 $175,000 in the year 2008*$175,000 in the year 2002 $175,000 in the year 2009*$175,000 in the year 2003 $175,000 in the year 2010*$175,000 in the year 2004 $175,000 in the year 2011*$175,000 in the year 2005(*Callable Maturities)The District reserves the right to  change the time and/or date of  the  bid  opening,  and  notice  thereof  shall  be provided at least 24 hours prior to the time set forth above and transmitted over the Thomson Municipal Newswire.Bids, accompanied  by  $43,540 good  faith  deposit check, must be for all  $2,177,000 bonds. Award  shall be based  on lowest net interest  cost. Legal opinion  to be provided  by Hawkins, Delafield &amp;amp;Wood.Bidders must  refer to  the full  Notice  of Sale  for the complete terms and  conditions of the  sale. Copies of  said Notice and the Official  Statement may be promptly  obtained from Munistat  Services,  Inc., 12  Roosevelt  Avenue,  Port Jefferson Station, New  York 11776;  phone: (516)  331-8888; fax: (516) 331-8834.Dated: August 13, 1997			  William F. Connors, Jr.		  President of the Board of Education			 and Chief Fiscal Officer			  (From The Bond Buyer)</detail><filename>808632newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>PHILIPPINES: El Nino seen stunting Philippine farm 1997 growth.</title><detail>Philippine agriculture growth slowed in the first half of the year and analysts said on Tuesday it could decelerate further this year if, as expected, the El Nino weather phenomenon causes a shortage of rain.Agriculture Secretary Salvador Escudero said the farm sector grew by 3.43 percent in the first six months of the year, well below the year earlier's 4.75 percent.In the first three months, the sector posted a healthy 4.22 percent growth, against just 2.49 percent in 1996.&amp;quot;I expect agricultural growth to settle within a range of two to three percent this year,&amp;quot; Rolando Dy, agribusiness director of the University of Asia and the Pacific, told Reuters.Early this year, Escudero said the sector, which accounts for 21 percent of the country's gross domestic output, could rise by 4.7 percent this year, up from last year's 3.9 percent.Dy, however, said rice harvests in the second half might be cut by the El Nino, and the weaker growth in the poultry sector could weigh down the overall sector.The Philippine weather bureau has forecast a prolonged dry spell starting late this year due to the freak weather phenomenon caused by warming of water in the western Pacific ocean, creating drought in some areas and heavier-than-usual rainfall in others.Gross output in the farm sector was valued at 122.7 billion pesos in the first half, Escudero said.Major crops, which contributed 39.9 percent of the output, grew by a slower 2.4 percent compared with 7.54 percent last year due to declines in unmilled rice and sugarcane harvests.Unmilled rice, which accounts for 13.03 percent of total output, dropped by 2.11 percent to 4.85 million tonnes in the first half of the year due to below-normal rainfall conditions and flooding in some areas.&amp;quot;There were also reports of pest infestations particularly in the Mindanao regions during the second quarter,&amp;quot; Escudero said.Dy also said he expected the poultry subsector to slow down for the rest of the year after heady growth in 1996.This year, growth in the poultry sector is expected to be tempered as industry players are reducing their capacities to cut the glut.The Philippine poultry sector grew by 10.25 percent in the first six months of the year, a notch higher the 10.24 percent growth in the year-ago period.</detail><filename>808558newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>AUSTRIA: OMV to slash around 1,000 jobs by 1999.</title><detail>Austrian oil and chemicals group OMV said on Tuesday it would slash around 1,000 staff by the end of 1998, and was taking out a two billion-schilling provision this year to cover severance and pension payments.OMV, whose workforce has been reduced to 8,500 by the end of last year from 12,660 in 1992, said it wanted to make savings worth some one billion schillings per year after its restructuring programme is complete.Around 203 employees left the company in the first half of the year and a total of 600 are expected to leave this full year and the next. But the company told a news conference it expected to employ another 200 over the period.Chief executive Richard Schenz, who said further job cuts were in the pipeline, said many employees who would be made redundant were 50 or 60 years old and would receive on average 4.5 million schillings over the next seven years from OMV, Austria's largest industrial group. -- Vienna newsroom +431 531 12256</detail><filename>809879newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>USA: U.S. municipal bond market indicators - update.</title><detail>DAILY INDICATORS				   Latest     Previous  Last DateBlue List  BLT735	 $1.229 bln  $1.297 bln   8/19/97Reuters 30-day Visible Supply   $7.021 bln  $6.898 bln   8/19/97 Competitive Visible     $1.229 bln  $1.182 bln   8/19/97 Negotiated Visible	$5.791 bln  $5.716 bln   8/19/97Bond Buyer 30-day Visible Supply   $3.557 bln  $3.671 bln   8/19/97 Competitive Visible     $1.436 bln  $1.460 bln   8/19/97 Negotiated Visible	$2.122 bln  $2.211 bln   8/19/97Bond Buyer 40-Bond Index	5.50%	 5.51%   8/19/97(yield to maturity)Lipper general muni index    131.36	131.39   8/15/97CRB Index			  237.68	239.13   8/18/97Lehman long govt index	   0.50	  0.01   8/18/97(total return)WEEKLY INDICATORSReuters 10-Year GO Index	4.74%	 4.63%   8/14/97Bond Buyer 20 Bond Index	5.42%	 5.33%   8/14/97Bond Buyer 11 Bond Index	5.35%	 5.25%   8/14/97Bond Buyer Revenue Bond Index 5.71%	 5.62%   8/14/97Bond Buyer 1-Year Note Index  3.87%	 3.76%   8/13/97PSA Municipal Swap Index	3.42%	 3.40%   8/13/97----------------------------------------------Moody's Weekly Municipal Bond Yield Averages			  Latest   Previous    Last Date    10-year Aaa	4.77%	4.62%	8/15/97    10-year Aa	 4.81%	4.68%	8/15/97    20-year Aaa	5.31%	5.19%	8/15/97    20-year Aa	 5.35%	5.24%	8/15/97    20-year A	  5.38%	5.28%	8/15/97    20-year Baa	5.41%	5.31%	8/15/97    VMIG weekly	3.42%	3.41%	8/15/97----------------------------------------------Delphis Hanover weekly muni bond yields calculated August 14.*		Aaa		Aa	     A	     Baa 1998    3.85  3.75    4.00  3.90   4.20  4.10   4.50  4.40 2002    4.30  4.20    4.50  4.40   4.70  4.60   5.00  4.90 2007    4.65  4.55    4.85  4.75   5.10  5.00   5.40  5.30 2012    5.05  4.95    5.20  5.10   5.45  5.35   5.75  5.65 2017    5.25  5.20    5.40  5.35   5.60  5.55   5.90  5.85 2022    5.30  5.25    5.45  5.40   5.65  5.60   5.95  5.90 2027    5.35  5.30    5.50  5.45   5.70  5.65   6.00  5.95*from previous calculation on August 7.--U.S. Municipal Desk, 212-859-1650</detail><filename>808628newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>USA: U.S. municipal bond market indicators -- update.</title><detail>DAILY INDICATORS				   Latest     Previous  Last DateBlue List  BLT735	 $1.229 bln  $1.297 bln   8/19/97Reuters 30-day Visible Supply   $6.898 bln  $6.599 bln   8/18/97 Competitive Visible     $1.182 bln  $1.207 bln   8/18/97 Negotiated Visible	$5.716 bln  $5.392 bln   8/18/97Bond Buyer 30-day Visible Supply   $3.671 bln  $3.645 bln   8/18/97 Competitive Visible     $1.460 bln  $1.408 bln   8/18/97 Negotiated Visible	$2.211 bln  $2.237 bln   8/18/97Bond Buyer 40-Bond Index	5.51%	 5.56%   8/18/97(yield to maturity)Lipper general muni index    131.36	131.39   8/15/97CRB Index  .CRB		 237.68	239.13   8/18/97Lehman long govt index	   0.50	  0.01   8/18/97(total return)WEEKLY INDICATORSReuters 10-Year GO Index	4.74%	 4.63%   8/14/97Bond Buyer 20 Bond Index	5.42%	 5.33%   8/14/97Bond Buyer 11 Bond Index	5.35%	 5.25%   8/14/97Bond Buyer Revenue Bond Index 5.71%	 5.62%   8/14/97Bond Buyer 1-Year Note Index  3.87%	 3.76%   8/13/97PSA Municipal Swap Index	3.42%	 3.40%   8/13/97----------------------------------------------Moody's Weekly Municipal Bond Yield Averages			  Latest   Previous    Last Date    10-year Aaa	4.77%	4.62%	8/15/97    10-year Aa	 4.81%	4.68%	8/15/97    20-year Aaa	5.31%	5.19%	8/15/97    20-year Aa	 5.35%	5.24%	8/15/97    20-year A	  5.38%	5.28%	8/15/97    20-year Baa	5.41%	5.31%	8/15/97    VMIG weekly	3.42%	3.41%	8/15/97----------------------------------------------Delphis Hanover weekly muni bond yields calculated August 14.*		Aaa		Aa	     A	     Baa 1998    3.85  3.75    4.00  3.90   4.20  4.10   4.50  4.40 2002    4.30  4.20    4.50  4.40   4.70  4.60   5.00  4.90 2007    4.65  4.55    4.85  4.75   5.10  5.00   5.40  5.30 2012    5.05  4.95    5.20  5.10   5.45  5.35   5.75  5.65 2017    5.25  5.20    5.40  5.35   5.60  5.55   5.90  5.85 2022    5.30  5.25    5.45  5.40   5.65  5.60   5.95  5.90 2027    5.35  5.30    5.50  5.45   5.70  5.65   6.00  5.95*from previous calculation on August 7.--U.S. Municipal Desk, 212-859-1650</detail><filename>809585newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>MEXICO: New Mexico to Mexico cattle export update -USDA.</title><detail>Weekly update of New Mexico cattle exports to Mexico, to Aug 16 - USDA.(Livestock per head, year in Jan/Dec calendar year).	Beef cattle		Week	     Year     Year Ago    Slaughter		     650	   19,615	  3,631    Calves			    0		  1		0    Breeding males, females     0	    1,787	    461	Dairy			Week	     Year     Year Ago    Breeding males, females     0	    5,990	   822((--Timna Tanners, Mexico City newsroom +525 728-7903))</detail><filename>808381newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>CHINA: China July tax revenue up 19.1 percent yr/yr.</title><detail>China collected 65.3 billion yuan ($7.87 billion) in industrial and commercial tax in July, up 19.1 percent from a year ago, the China Daily said on Tuesday.The figure includes revenues from an increase in the stamp duty on share trading and a business tax on finance companies introduced in May.If revenues from the increases were excluded, the increase would only be 8.2 percent year-on-year, the lowest growth rate since January, the newspaper said, quoting officials of the State General Administration of Taxation.Officials attributed the slowdown to low efficiency in enterprises in the hot summer weather and payment delays.Domestic consumption tax revenue fell for the first time, down 4.2 percent from a year earlier, and VAT revenue rose only 2.9 percent after averaging 12.9 percent growth in the first half of this year, China Daily said.Industrial and commercial tax revenues in the first seven months totalled 423 billion yuan, up 68.8 billion yuan from the same 1996 period, it said.China's industrial and commercial tax revenue target for the year is 695 billion yuan, compared with collections of 644.6 billion yuan last year, the newspaper said.China collected 12.34 billion yuan in personal income tax in the first half of this year, up 42.5 percent from the same period last year, the Economic Information Daily said.($1 = 8.3 yuan)-- Beijing Newsroom (86) 10-6532-1921; Fax 10-6532-4978</detail><filename>810364newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>NEW ZEALAND: NZ non-res building consents up 3.9 pct in June yr.</title><detail>New Zealand non-residential building consents rose in value by 3.9 percent in the year to June to NZ$2.38 billion, Statistics NZ (SNZ) said on Tuesday.Consents for residential buildings rose 1.6 percent to a value of NZ$3.58 billion in the June year.  Non-residential consents worth $164.8 million were issued in June, down from from $283.9 million in May.Consents for 22,598 new dwelling units were issued in the June year, 1.8 percent more than in the June 1996 year. The national median consent value for new dwelling units was $110,000.The total value of all building consents issued in the year was $5.96 billion, up 2.5 percent from the June 1996 year.-- Wellington newsroom 64 4 4734 746, fax 4736 212	 email wellington.newsroom@reuters.com</detail><filename>810143newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>UKRAINE: Ukraine ends ban on grain movement-trade.</title><detail>Grain within Ukraine is moving freely again after many regions refused to release it earlier this month until state grain orders were met, Western experts said on Tuesday.&amp;quot;The bans are pretty well off,&amp;quot; said Bohdan Chomiak of Chemonics International, a U.S.-funded group working to develop the agriculture sector in the former Soviet republic.&amp;quot;Everyone raised a hue and cry and they were successful this year,&amp;quot; he said.This year's limits on grain movement recalled a situation a year ago, when grain exchanges stopped working and many trading companies lost money after the government quietly ordered grain to remain in silos until state orders were filled.Ukraine has promised to do away with the Soviet-era practice of grain buying by the state, often at below-market prices, next year. This year's order was set at 5.88 million tonnes against 5.00 million tonnes in 1996.Ukraine has forecast a grain harvest of 37-38 million tonnes this year compared to 25.4 million tonnes in 1996.U.S. ambassador to Ukraine William Miller, who lobbied on behalf of U.S. companies denied pre-purchased grain this year, said President Leonid Kuchma, Prime Minister Valery Pustovoitenko and Agriculture Minister Yuri Karasyk had promised to ensure grain would be released.&amp;quot;They have given the order that there be open trade in these matters,&amp;quot; Miller told Reuters.The government has never formally admitted to issuing orders last year placing bans on grain movements, but top officials have promised such bans would never happen again.--Irene Marushko, Kiev Newsroom +380 44 244-9150e-mail: moscow.newsroom@reuters.com</detail><filename>808148newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>NEW ZEALAND: NZ SPORT - Cooper wants a few new faces in Chiefs.</title><detail>HAMILTON, Aug 19 - When new Waikato Chiefs rugby coach Ross Cooper watches the NPC competition this year he'll be looking for a tighthead prop and first five-eighth to include in next year's squad, NZPA reports.Cooper, a national selector since 1993, was today named the Chiefs new coach, replacing Brad Meurant who quit after this year's Super 12.New Zealand Maori coach Matt Te Pou will be his assistant, replacing current Waikato NPC coach John Boe.  Cooper said most of this year's squad would form the basis of next year's Chiefs, but NPC form would also influence selections.He was pleased with the opening round form of Waikato, Bay of Plenty and Northland, who each had wins, and felt King Country would improve, as would North Harbour when their All Blacks returned. Those five unions make up the Chiefs.Cooper said he would use the draft system to beef up his squad and wanted a good tighthead prop and first five-eighth, and lock Mark Cooksley back from the Wellington Hurricanes.  He said he was disappointed with the Chiefs' performances in 1996 and 1997, when they finished sixth and 11th respectively, and it was time the team played to their potential.&amp;quot;That's important to me, that people look at the team and can honestly say we have played to our potential.&amp;quot;We have had two years of not good performances, it's now up to the players, coaches and team management to get the team up there.&amp;quot;Chiefs captain Ian Jones said Cooper's appointment was exciting.  &amp;quot;Ross has learned the All Black way of doing things and he'll bring that blue print to the Chiefs,&amp;quot; he said.Jones said he anticipated most of the changes would be in how the team was organised, rather than playing tactics or game plan.Te Pou said he had some homework to do as he had been busy with New Zealand Maori this year and hadn't watched many of the Chiefs games.But he was confident the side's fortunes could be turned around.  &amp;quot;The ability is there, it's when you don't have the ability that you have your work cut out. When you have the ability it's a matter of harnessing that ability.&amp;quot;Te Pou coached Bay of Plenty in 1993 and 1994 and has been unbeaten with New Zealand Maori in his three years as coach, and one as assistant coach.</detail><filename>807999newsML.xml</filename></pp></docs>