<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><docs><pp><title>USA: U.S. CREDIT MARKET OUTLOOK - Whither the economy?.</title><detail>The Treasury's refunding next week will  occupy the attention of debt market participants, as they continue  to sort out what this past week's full menu of economic data means  for the U.S. economy.The Treasury will sell $16 billion in three-year notes, $12.0 billion  in 10-year notes and $10.0 billion in 30-year bonds next Tuesday,  Wednesday and Thursday.  Market players said the refunding should  occupy more attention than next week's economic data which will include  the Federal Reserve's Beige Book, June chain store sales and June  consumer credit.  After a barrage of surprisingly strong economic data sent 30-year  Treasury bonds plummeting more than two points Friday, &amp;quot;The refunding  will be the central focus of next week,&amp;quot; said Joseph Liro, chief economist  at CIBC Wood Gundy.&amp;quot;I doubt if the Beige Book will give any indication of a Fed move,&amp;quot;  Liro said. &amp;quot;The real focus is how the market handles the supply,&amp;quot;After Friday's back-up in rates, said Liro, &amp;quot;It should be a lot easier  to take down these auctions than when it was with the 10-year note  below 6.0 percent which is where it was before the jobs number.&amp;quot;   The market was stunned by Friday's July jobs data that was much stronger  than expected;  the unemployment rate fell to 4.8 percent and 316,000  nonfarm jobs were created. Then the National Association of Purchasing  Management index of July manufacturing activity rose to 58.6 percent,  its highest in 2-1/2 years. Meanwhile, the University of Michigan  released its July final index of consumer sentiment, which soared  to an all-time high of 107.1 from 104.5 in the final June report.Treasury prices, which rallied for for consecutive days through Thursday  fell sharply Friday amid repeated signs the nation's economy may be  stronger than the market had thought.  &amp;quot;The economy is showing some strengthening in the third quarter and  interest rates have shown significant declines. Some of the euphoria  is now coming out of the market,&amp;quot; said Lynn Reaser, chief economist  at Barnett Bank Inc.Prior to Friday's strong data, Reaser contended, next week's refunding  was &amp;quot;largely discounted in the market.&amp;quot;She said June consumer credit data, to be released Thursday, Augusts  7, could provide clues to consumer confidence. Otherwise, Reaser said,  &amp;quot;It should be a pretty slow week in terms of numbers. The market will  be adjusting to this week's numbers which showed some rebound in July.&amp;quot;   John Williams, managing director and chief global markets economist  at Bankers Trust Co, agreed that participants in the Treasury market  &amp;quot;likely will digest the blizzard of data it got this week.&amp;quot;People are looking to see if there is any hint of a strong second  half in the nation's economy,&amp;quot; said Williams, referring to the Fed's  beige book, to be released Wednesday, August 6..&amp;quot;I suspect that it will confirm there is a lot of economic momentum.  The market's euphoria has been built on a benign inflation backdrop,&amp;quot;  he added.  &amp;quot;If the economy shows some strengthening we can move to 6.5 percent  to 7.0 percent, particuarly if the economy shows signs of strengthening  and talk of a (Federal Reserve) tightening later in the year crops  up,&amp;quot; Reaser said.Reaser said she believed signs of vigor hinted at by Friday's economic  data may reignite expectations of a Federal Reserve interest rate  move later this year. &amp;quot;Employment and the purchasing management index  all show the economy is far from dead,&amp;quot; she said.Williams noted that Treasury prices gave &amp;quot;quite a concession&amp;quot; Friady  and &amp;quot;the refunding next week will go OK at these levels.&amp;quot;Liro predicted next week's refunding should pick up momentum as the  week progresses. So, while three-year notes may not see as lively  investor interest, the 30-year bonds should be well received, he said.(( -- U.S. Mortgage Unit, 212-859-1668 ))</detail><filename>772933newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>BULGARIA: BULGARIA SEES Q2 CURRENT ACCOUNT SURPLUS - OFFICIAL.</title><detail>Bulgaria expects to sustain its current account  surplus in the second quarter after a $234.7 million surplus in the  first quarter and a $22.3 million gap in 1996, a Bulgarian National  Bank (BNB) official said on Friday.BNB preliminary figures show the current account surplus stood at  some $500 million at end-May against a gap of over $500 million a  year earlier due to a rising trade surplus and a capital inflow.&amp;quot;The trend towards increase in the current account surplus is expected  to continue in the second quarter. There are no expectations of a  reversal in the trend,&amp;quot; the official, who declined to be named told  Reuters.Bulgaria took steps to slow inflation and the lev's depreciation prior  to implementation of a currency board fixed exchange rate regime on  July 1.Direct investment rose to $240 million in the first five months of  this year from $67 million for the same period of 1996 due to financial  stabilisation and Bulgaria's moves to speed up privatisation.Portfolio investment rose to $135 million at end-May from $20.5 million  in the first quarter, mainly because of increased foreign investment  in high yield government securities.An outflow of short-term investment of $59 million was registered  in the first five months of 1996, which increased to $169 million  at end-1996.Exports of fuels, metals and mineral resources rose in the first five  months while exports of agricultural produce fell.Due to the sharp lev depreciation imports decreased by more than 20  percent from January through May year on year with the biggest fall  posted in imports of investment goods and imports from the European  Union.The lev fell to around 3,000 to the dollar in February from around  500 at end-1996 before recovering to around 1,600 in May.BNB foreign exchange reserves rose to $1.28 billion at end-May from  $600 million a year earlier.The BNB publishes current and capital account figures quarterly. Figures  for the secound quarter were expected to be released at mid-August.  -- Sofia Newsroom +359-2 981 4145</detail><filename>771974newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>SWEDEN: PRESS DIGEST - Sweden - Aug 1.</title><detail>Following are some of the leading stories  in the Swedish papers this morning. Reuters has not verified these  stories and does not vouch for their accuracy.DAGENS NYHETER- The strong U.S. dollar has given Swedish exporters a boost. This  year the dollar has strengthened by 20 percent and this week even  passed the magical 8.00 crowns level briefly. The currency was last  at this level in March 1994.- Sweden is enjoying its biggest grain crop since 1990. This year's  harvest will be even bigger than last year's harvest, with an increase  of four percent in plantings to 1.27 million hectares. The warm weather  that started at the beginning of July has helped the crop.- July was statistically a good month for the Stockholm bourse that  rose 5.6 percent. Sharemarkets in Amsterdam and Frankfurt rose 15  percent and 18 percent respectively.- Vehicle maker AB Volvo sold its 11.38 percent stake in French car  maker Renault for 5.9 billion crowns. The buyer was investment bank  Union Bank of Switzerland. It was part of the company's divestment  strategy to concentrate on core businesses.SVENSKA DAGBLADET- The ruling Social Democrats promised that noone under 25 years old  will be unemployed for more than 100 days. But more and more young  people are unemployed for long periods. In June 15,693 young people  were out of work for more than 100 days which was an increase of 25  percent from a year before.- Insurer Skandia's subsidiary Vesta is on the short list of financial  institutions to manage the billions of dollars made from Norway's  oil industry. The Norwegian government want to increase the returns  from the state's oil fund.- Swedish investment company Custos, that does not have Ericsson in  its portfolio, has risen strongly in the first half of 1997. Its shares  have seen an average return of 21 percent this year and the company  is satisfied with these levels.DAGENS INDUSTRI- Public criticism of taxes on property has pushed the government  to reconsider the levels. Tax Minister Thomas Ostros and Interior  Minister Jorgen Andersson have this summer discussed lowering the  tax from 1.7 to 1.5 percent.- This autumn will give Information Technology companies a rough ride  on the Stockholm bourse, according to managing director of Intentia,  Bjorn Algkvist. He said there has been a shortage of good sector analysts  to date but this is changing.- Ferry operators have so far this summer seen an increase in volumes  of about 10 percent but there has not been any discussions about increasing  prices.- Vehicle maker AB Volvo is boosting its investment programme in Brazil  to 2.87 billion crowns. This means that its tryck FH12 Globetrotter  will start to be produced in Brazil from 1998. However managing director  of Volvo Brazil, Carl Lindestrom, says there are no plans for car  production.-- Belinda Goldsmith, Stockholm newsroom +46-8-700 1017</detail><filename>774325newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>GREECE: ATHLETICS-PROFILE OF MEN'S WORLD SHOT PUT CHAMPION BAGACH.</title><detail>Profile of Aleksandr Bagach, who won the world men's shot put title on Saturday: Born November 21, 1966. Matusov, UkraineBanned for two years for excessive testoterone levels in 1989 when he finished third in the European Cup.In 1993 he took bronze at the Stuttgart world championships, moving up to third place after American Mike Stulce was disqualified for doping.The following year, he became the first athlete representing Ukraine to win a European indoor title.In May this year, he improved his best mark with an effort of 21.47 metres. He equalled that mark on Saturday.</detail><filename>810658newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>BULGARIA: Bulgaria sees Q2 c/a surplus - central bank source.</title><detail>Bulgaria expects its current account to remain  in the black in the second quarter following a $234.7 million surplus  in the first quarter and a $22.3 million deficit for 1996, a Bulgarian  National Bank (BNB) official said on Friday.BNB preliminary figures show the current account surplus stood at  some $500 million at end-May against a gap of over $500 million a  year earlier due to a rising trade surplus and an influx of capital.&amp;quot;The trend towards increase in the current account surplus is expected  to continue in the second quarter. There are no expectations of a  reversal in the trend,&amp;quot; the official, who declined to be named, told  Reuters.Bulgaria took steps to check inflation and the lev's depreciation  prior to implementation of a currency board fixed exchange rate regime  on July 1.Direct investment rose to $240 million in the first five months of  this year from $67 million for the same period in 1996 thanks to greater  financial stability and Bulgaria's moves to speed up privatisation.Portfolio investment rose to $135 million at end-May from $20.5 million  in the first quarter, mainly due to higher foreign investment in high-yield  government securities.A $59 million outflow of short-term investment was registered in the  first five months of 1996, increasing to $169 million at end-1996.Exports of fuels, metals and mineral resources rose in the first five  months, while exports of agricultural produce fell.A sharp depreciation in the lev meant imports decreased by more than  20 percent from January through May year on year, with the biggest  fall posted in imports of investment goods and imports from the European  Union.The lev fell to around 3,000 to the dollar in February from around  500 at end-1996 before recovering to around 1,600 in May.BNB foreign exchange reserves rose to $1.28 billion at end-May from  $600 million a year earlier.The BNB publishes current and capital account figures quarterly. Figures  for the second quarter are expected to be released at mid-August.-- Sofia Newsroom +359-2 981 4145</detail><filename>772080newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>PHILIPPINES: Philippines' UCPB first half net at 1.22 bln pesos.</title><detail>The Philippine's United Coconut Planters Bank (UCBP) posted a consolidated net income of 1.22 billion pesos for the first half of the year against 1.14 billion a year ago.The bank said in a statement released on Saturday that its loan volume rose 15 percent during the period to 55.24 billion pesos compared with 47.92 billion the first half of last year.The bank said increased loans to the middle market, companies with annual audited sales below 250 million pesos, accounted for the bulk of loans extended during the period.Its deposit volume rose 10 percent to 50.23 billion pesos for the first six months of the year from 45.76 billion a year ago, the bank added.The company said its brokerage unit, UCPB Securities, earned 19.5 million pesos as of end-June from 6.66 million last year.UCBP Rural Bank made 64.62 million pesos in net profits while its investment banking unit, UCBP Capital Corp, registered a 107.79 million peso net income.Unlisted UCBP is one of the top 10 banks in the country. Most of its shares were sequestered by the government on suspicion that they were owned by a close business associate of the late former president Ferdinand Marcos.-- Manila newsroom (63 2) 8418939 Fax 8176267</detail><filename>810792newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>ITALY: Italy July PSBR 4.3 trillion lire - Treasury.</title><detail>Italy's public sector borrowing requirement  was 4.3 trillion lire in July 1997, some 5.55 trillion lire less than  the same month last year, the Treasury said in a statement.It added that Italy's cumulative PSBR in the first seven months of  the year was 29.75 trillion lire, some 33.5 trillion lire less than  the January-to-July period in 1996.  The July data keeps Italy on track to meet its goal of a state deficit  of three percent of gross domestic product this year, as demanded  by the Maastricht Treaty for countries wishing to sign up to the planned  single European currency.Italy's deficit/GDP ratio was 6.7 percent in 1996. -- Rome newsroom  +396 6782501</detail><filename>774142newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>USA: USDA daily cattle and hog slaughter - August 1.</title><detail>Est daily livestock slaughter under Fed inspection - USDA					  Cattle	 Calves    HogsFriday     08/01/97  (est)	131,000	6,000     318,000Week ago (est)			128,000	6,000     315,000Year ago (act)			131,000	7,000     310,000Saturday   08/02/97  (est)	 78,000	    0	 4,000Week to date (est)		  731,000     28,000   1,586,000Same Period Last Week (est)     706,000     27,000   1,616,000Same Period Last Year* (act)    668,000     34,000   1,629,0001997 Year to date		21,148,000    882,000  50,796,0001996 Year to date*	     21,459,000    980,000  52,823,000Percent change			  -1.4%     -10.0%	 -3.8%*1996 totals adjusted to reflect NASS revisions1997 Totals are subject to revisionYearly totals may not add due to roundingPrevious day estimated    Steer and Heifer   Cow and BullThursday				107,000	     25,000((Chicago newsdesk 312-408 8720))</detail><filename>773148newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>SWEDEN: Swedish car registrations rose 35.3 pct July-SCB.</title><detail>New registrations of cars in Sweden rose  35.3 percent to 18,089 vehicles in July compared to July a year earlier,  Statistics Sweden (SCB) said on Friday.An increase of 14.2 percent was noted for lorries in July when 1,419  lorries were registered.  The figures include private imports and all registrations of both  old and new cars.The Association of Swedish Automobile Manfacturers and Wholesalers  said on Friday that registrations of new cars, excluding private imports  and cars older than three years, rose 13 percent in July from a year  ago to 13,400 vehicles.-- Birgitta Forsberg, Stockholm newsroom +46-8-700 1006</detail><filename>774308newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>UK: India seen pressed to reach forecast sugar output.</title><detail>India could struggle to reach its official sugar output forecast of 13 million tonnes white value as few factories are still open at the end of this season's crop, E D &amp;amp; F Man said in a report on Monday.Just six factories were open by June 15, compared with 168 at the same stage last year, Man said.Projections for next year continued to suggest a much lower crop and speculation was mounting about the potential level of exports for next season, it added.In its previous report, Man estimated Indian sugar production at 13 million tonnes for 1996/97 after the bumper 13.2 million turned out the previous year. --Jeremy Smith, London Newsroom +44 171 542 8064</detail><filename>774480newsML.xml</filename></pp></docs>