<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><docs><pp><title>SWITZERLAND: Kuoni sees 1997 net up at least 30 pct.</title><detail>Swiss travel and tour group Kuoni Reisen Holding AG said it expected net profit to rise at least 30 percent this year from 1996's 69.4 million Swiss francs.Kuoni also said it expected the dividend on 1997 results to be within a pay-out ratio between 30 and 35 percent set by the group's dividend policy.  Kuoni is active mainly in Europe, Britain and Asian emerging markets.&amp;quot;Barring exceptional events, operating profit should develop at a clearly stronger rate than sales,&amp;quot; Kuoni said in a statement on half-year results.It projected sales would grow about 20 percent from last year, in part due to acquisitions.&amp;quot;Group net profit should rise by at least 30 percent from last year and reach a new record level,&amp;quot; Kuoni said.It said the board of directors expected to ask shareholders next May 15 to approve a dividend &amp;quot;in line with the dividend policy (pay-out ratio: 30-35 percent)&amp;quot;.Kuoni posted a 139 percent leap in net profit in the first six months of 1997 to 33 million Swiss francs on sales of 1.9 billion, 25 percent more than in the first half of 1996.Currency factors caused by a weaker Swiss franc this year -- especially against sterling -- contributed 39.5 percent of the jump in net profit, it said.-- Zurich Newsroom, +41-1-631 7340</detail><filename>809035newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>GERMANY: AMB sees higher earnings for full-year.</title><detail>German insurance and financial group Aachener und Muenchener Beteiligungs AG (AMB) said on Tuesday it expected earnings in full-year 1997 to increase.&amp;quot;If claims do not worsen substantially and if growth in the capital markets does not deteriorate appreciably, then we expect earnings above last year's level,&amp;quot; the group said in its interim statement.In 1996, AMB reported group net profit of 343.6 million marks.The company reiterated its forecast that it would keep dividends at the previous year's level of 16 marks.The group said that consolidated net profit in the first half of the year was 131 million marks, compared to 126 million marks in the same period a year ago, while pretax profit rose to 176 million marks from 171 million.Group premium income in the period rose to 8.9 billion marks from 8.6 billion.AMB is 33.5 percent-owned by the French insurance group AGF. Germany's Dresdner Bank holds 14.7 percent, Munich Re holds 8.6 percent and Allianz holds five percent, with 38.2 percent held by small shareholders.The group said it expected to save 400 million marks annually as a result of restructuring measures involving closer cooperation between the group's subsidiaries.The number of employees also fell by 400 people to 18,500.--Clifford Coonan, Frankfurt Newsroom +49 69 756525</detail><filename>810534newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>AUSTRALIA: Bendigo plans profitability lift in 97/98.</title><detail>Regional banking group Bendigo Bank Ltd said on Tuesday continued strong growth in lending should help build profitability in the year to June 30, 1998.Earlier, Bendigo reported a fall in net profit to A$11.04 million forn the year to June 30, 1997, compared with A$12.73 million a year earlier.Bendigo said its home loan portfolio made up 74 percent of its total loans at June 30, compared with 89 percent a year ago.&amp;quot;We anticipate that this shift in emphasis, aided by continued strong growth in lending, should assist in restoring core profitability in 1997/98,&amp;quot; the bank said.  Bendigo managing director Rob Hunt said in a statement the bank had positioned itself to grow its 1997/98 profit even on a substantially reduced net interest margin.The bank said the 1996/97 profit fall was mainly due to a reduction of 64 basis points in the net interest margins.&amp;quot;We accepted that the reduction in home loan margins is permanent and that margins will not return to their historic levels,&amp;quot; chairman Richard Guy said in the same statement.&amp;quot;It is therefore vital that we restructure our operations to pursue alternative income sources without compromising our credit standards,&amp;quot; Guy said.  At 10.55 a.m. (0055 GMT), Bendigo shares were unchanged at A$4.50.-- Sydney newsroom 61-2 9373-1800</detail><filename>810162newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>GERMANY: FOCUS-AMB expects AM Group 97 earnings rise.</title><detail>German insurance and financial holding group Aachener und Muenchener Beteiligungs AG (AMB) said on Tuesday that it expected earnings at its insurance unit AM group in full-year 1997 to increase.&amp;quot;If claims do not worsen substantially and if growth in the capital markets does not worsen appreciably, then we expect a result at AM group above last year's level,&amp;quot; the holding company for AMB said in its interim statement.In 1996 AMB reported group net profit of 343.6 million marks ($187.4 million).&amp;quot;The earning situation of AMB in the first six months was satisfactory and gives reason to expect that for 1997 we will also be in a position to pay a 32 percent dividend,&amp;quot; AMB said in a letter to shareholders.AMB also reiterated a previous forecast that it would keep dividends at the previous year's level of 16 marks.AMB said that net profit in the first half of the year was 131 million marks, compared to 126 million marks, while pre-tax profit at the group rose to 176 million marks from 171 million.Group premium income at the AM Group in the period rose to 8.9 billion marks from 8.6 billion.&amp;quot;The premium income for direct insurance business went up by 4.4 percent to 8.9 billion marks. The business abroad included in that figure even grew by 7.7 percent to 877 miilion marks, which is above all attributable to the good development of the Dutch subsidiaries,&amp;quot; AMB said.It said that both its life insurance unit and its property and casualty insurers outperformed the market average, while health insurance managed to continue last year's &amp;quot;satisfactory performance&amp;quot;.The group's claims ratio, which refers to expenditure on claims and surrenders as a percentage of total premiums, for direct business was 57 percent and remained at last year's level.Total expense ratio, which is commissions and expenses for all functional areas charged to the business year as a percentage of total premiums, for direct business was down by one percentage point to 18 percent.AMB is 33.5 percent-owned by the French insurance group AGF. Germany's Dresdner Bank holds 14.7 percent, Munich Re holds 8.6 percent and Allianz holds five percent, with 38.2 percent held by small shareholders.The group said it expected to save 400 million marks on annual costs as a result of its ongoing restructuring measures involving closer cooperation between the group's subsidiaries.The number of employees also narrowed by 400 people to 18,500.AMB said last month that it was looking forward to a steady future amid lower costs despite being knocked from the No.2 spot in German insurance by the recently-formed Ergo group.Ergo is made up of Munich Re's primary insurance unit and Victoria Holding. ($ = 1.834 German Marks)</detail><filename>809887newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>JAPAN: VW Japan confident of reaching 1997 target.</title><detail>Volkswagen Group Japan KK (VW Japan), the Japanese unit of Volkswagen AG, said on Tuesday it is confident it will achieve its sales target of 56,000 cars in 1997.&amp;quot;We are sure to achieve our target of 56,000 cars this year, but we hope we won't face supply shortages late this year because of strong demand for VW products worldwide,&amp;quot; VW Japan president Mitsuru Sato told Reuters.The 1997 target is up more than 10 percent from the company's 1996 sales of 50,290 cars.According to industry data, in the January-to-July period of this year, Japanese sales of VW cars rose 16.6 percent from the year-ago period to 32,419 units, despite an 11.5 percent drop in overall Japanese sales of imported cars to 210,464 in the same period. The overall decline was attributed mainly to an increase in Japan's sales tax in April.Sato said the impact of the higher sales tax was still hurting car sales.VW Japan introduced a new Passat sedan model in Japan on Tuesday with a sales target of 2,000 units by the end of 1997.Sato said VW Japan plans to sell 2,850 new Passats in 1998.The Japanese price for the new model with an 11-year warranty and a fully galvanised body to protect against rust and corrosion, will start at 2,975,000 yen.- Tokyo Equities Desk (813) 3432-9404email: tokyo.equities.newsroom@reuters.com</detail><filename>808573newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>ARGENTINA: Argentine tax evasion $40 bln a year - congressman.</title><detail>Tax evasion in Argentina totals $40 billion a year, which is more than 10 percent of gross domestic product, or equivalent to the annual budget, the Lower House of Congress' budget committee leader said.But committee chairman Oscar Lamberto, a deputy for the ruling Peronist Party, said the situation had improved in recent years because more tax dodgers were in jail.&amp;quot;We're not doing great, but we're much better off than two or three years ago, when there were 8,000 (evasion) cases in court and no arrests. Today there are less cases and more people detained for sums involving more than $1.0 million,&amp;quot; Lamberto told local radio Tuesday.In separate comments to newspapers, he said $21 billion in value added tax and $19 billion in income taxes were evaded yearly, a calculation he said was based on &amp;quot;what the Treasury should collect in revenue as related to annual GDP.&amp;quot;&amp;quot;Numbers show that tax evasion in Argentina ranks among the highest in the world,&amp;quot; Lamberto said.He favored lowering the VAT and employer payroll taxes to improve collection, and noted that without such high levels of tax evasion, &amp;quot;We wouldn't have a fiscal deficit or have to ask for foreign financing.&amp;quot;Argentina is expected to show a budget deficit of $5.0 billion this year, according to International Monetary Fund estimates.((-- Carmen Pignotti, Buenos Aires Newsroom 541 318-0657))</detail><filename>808403newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>BURUNDI: Burundi expects to resume cotton export next year.</title><detail>Burundi cotton officials said on Tuesday cotton production was expected to pick up next year with exports to begin again after a year of no sales abroad.&amp;quot;We are hoping to produce about 6,000 tonnes next year, so we'd be exporting about 1,200 tonnes,&amp;quot; Francois Kabura, Director of Burundi's state-run cotton company, COGERCO, told Reuters.He estimated total production for the 1996/97 crop, being harvested now, at between 2,600-3,000 tonnes, a yield which he said matched local demand and was being sold locally.Regional states imposed economic and transport sanctions against Burundi in July last year after an army coup but the Burundian government expects them to be completely lifted by next year.Cotton production in Burundi has fallen by about 70 percent since civil war broke out in 1993. Before that, production peaked at about 8,800 tonnes and the company was exporting an average of just under 2,400 tonnes of cotton fibre annually.But Kabura said COGERCO would not export any cotton this year and the company exported only 150 tonnes in 1996 and 202 tonnes in 1995.About 60 percent of the cotton COGERCO takes from farmers is cotton seed, manufactured locally into oil, while the remaining 40 percent is cotton fibre, of which about half is exported.Kabura said production had suffered most in the northern provinces of Cibitoke and Bubanza, both hard-hit by the civil war, but production in the east of Burundi was comparatively unaffected.&amp;quot;The security situation has improved in some areas, and the population which cultivates has returned home,&amp;quot; said Kabura, adding that output was expected to increase next year.Before the civil war, Burundi's cotton was primarily exported to markets in France, bringing in just under five percent of Burundi's foreign currency receipts, Kabura said.COGERCO officials say the company buys cotton from farmers at about 85 Burundi francs per kg but the cotton sells locally for about 500 Burundi francs per kg after manufacturing.Burundi's cotton season starts in November, while the crop is harvested from June to August.($1=359.71 Burundian francs)</detail><filename>808097newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>UK: FOCUS-Laura Ashley warns of gloomy profits.</title><detail>British fashion group Laura Ashley Holdings Plc on Tuesday warned of sharply-lower profits and said its long-awaited turnaround would be delayed by this year's disappointing results.The company, famous for its floral prints and taffeta party frocks, said it would post a first-half pretax loss of 4.5 million pounds ($7.2 million), followed by a lower-than-expected second-half profit and breakeven results for the year.The first-half loss included a one million pound charge for the closure of factories at Caernarfon and Machynlleth in Wales, resulting in about 190 job cuts, representing nearly five percent of its total workforce.The company also planned to cut back its U.S. expansion programme, opening only 13 stores this year and none next year due to losses there.The U.S. expansion has formed a major part of chief executive Ann Iverson's recovery strategy since she was hired to turn around the company.Iverson, an American, said this year's setbacks meant that Laura Ashley's recovery would take longer than the three-to-four year period she had predicted when she joined the firm in 1995.&amp;quot;Clearly, this year is going to be disappointing, but once we correct the problems that we've identified, I think we will get back into the turnaround. So it has been delayed,&amp;quot; she told Reuters in an interview.Laura Ashley's shares firmed 1.5 pence to 58 by 1030 GMT after falling sharply on Monday on worries about the firm's outlook.Traders said the profit warning -- the second in four months -- was unwelcome, but not as bad as some investors had expected following a series of management upheavals and disappointing results at the firm.&amp;quot;America is clearly the major problem,&amp;quot; said SocGen analyst Nick Bubb. &amp;quot;Ann Iverson put a lot of her personal stock of credibility into the American expansion programme, so she clearly is under a lot of pressure.&amp;quot;But Iverson said she planned to continue with her strategy, focusing on repositioning the Laura Ashley brand and improving the company's infrastructure.&amp;quot;When you see the problems, or more importantly the scale of them, the first port of call is to take action, and that's clearly what we're doing,&amp;quot; she said.When asked whether she planned to stay with the firm, she said, &amp;quot;Absolutely. I am still very committed, and I look forward to bringing the potential of the brand to fruition.&amp;quot;Laura Ashley's total like-for-like shop sales rose 11 percent in the first half to July 26. Taking the pound's strength into account, sales increased five percent.However, gross margins fell to 40.5 percent in the first half, due to a slowdown in home furnishings sales, compared to 48.4 percent in the year-ago period.&amp;quot;They have had quite good sales figures, but the sting in the tail is the huge fall in their gross margin in the first half,&amp;quot; analyst Bubb said. ($ = 0.622 British Pounds)</detail><filename>809390newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>INDIA: India Tata Chem sales at 16.2 bln rupees.</title><detail>Sales of Tata Chemicals Ltd rose to 16.24 billion rupees in the year ended March 31, 1997 from 15.34 billion a year earlier, the firm said on Tuesday.  Net profit fell to 2.5 billion rupees against 3.9 billion in 1995/96 due to the government's delay in setting a revised price for urea, it said.&amp;quot;The directors regret to report that the retention price for urea has not yet been finalised by the government,&amp;quot; the statement said.&amp;quot;In the meantime the government has notified a provisional price which is lower than the retention price that the company had asked for,&amp;quot; it said, adding the profit for 1995/96 and 1994/95 was based on the retention price.The profits in the past two years would have been lower by 1.97 billion rupees if it had been computed on the provisional price, it added.--Bombay Newsroom (91) 22-265-9000; Fax (91) 22-264 1699</detail><filename>809124newsML.xml</filename></pp><pp><title>USA: Fed holds key U.S. interest rates steady.</title><detail>The U.S. Federal Reserve on Tuesday left key interest rates unchanged amid clear evidence the nation's economy is growing at a comfortable speed with low inflation.The announcement by the central bank's Federal Open Market Committee (FOMC) was widely expected and left the key federal funds rate which banks charge each other for overnight loans steady at 5.5 percent.&amp;quot;The Federal Open Market Committee meeting ended at 12:40 (1640 GMT),&amp;quot; central bank spokesman Joe Coyne said. &amp;quot;There is no further announcement.&amp;quot;With recent data suggesting that growth is moderate and inflation steady in the world's dominant economy, investors had little reason to expect any change in the Fed's policy stance now.However, some analysts believe the central bank may move to tighten credit later in the year as faster growth raises the risk of higher inflation. The next FOMC meetings are set for Sept. 30 and Nov. 12.&amp;quot;There's a 50-50 chance that the Fed could hike interest rates in September and probably a better than a 50-50 chance of a move on Nov. 12. There are a number of reasons, the primary one being economic growth,&amp;quot; said Sung Won Sohn, chief economist at Norwest Corp. in Minneapolis.Financial markets took the news of steady rates in stride and reaction to the announcement was muted. The Dow Jones industrial average was some 50 points higher, while the yield on the key 30-year Treasury bond was steady at 6.52 percent.Fed Chairman Alan Greenspan last month prepared markets for a spell of steady rates when he said the central bank was ready to tighten credit if necessary to fend off inflation but hinted it may be a while until it needed to so so.The Fed last changed interest rates in March when it raised the federal funds rate by a quarter percentage point in a preemptive bid to choke off potential inflationary dangers.Overall growth in the economy dipped to 2.2 percent in the second quarter of the year from a breakneck pace of 4.9 percent in the January-March period as consumer spending slowed and unsold inventories began to build up.Inflation so far this year has increased at its slowest pace in 11 years and producer prices in July dropped for an record seventh month in a row. Real wages have declined even though the U.S. labor market remains tight.Higher interest rates would have raised the cost of borrowing money and ultimately dampened economic activity by putting a lid on spending and new investment.The attention has now shifted to this year's three remaining Fed meetings in September, November and December.Analysts are split whether the central bank may be prompted to raise rates later in the year if third quarter growth -- widely predicted to have recovered from the second quarter -- should raise inflation worries.&amp;quot;The odds favor that there will be a tightening at some point. It's a tough call ... but I would say it slightly favors fourth quarter still,&amp;quot; said William Dudley, chief economist at Wall Street broker Goldman, Sachs &amp;amp; Co. Inc.The Fed is expected to keep a particularly close watch on a tentative agreement to end a 15-day strike by the Teamsters union against United Parcel Service, widely seen as a victory for U.S. organized labor.Analysts have warned that sweeping concessions by the nation's biggest package delivery company could feed through into upward pressure on wages in other parts of the economy, potentially fueling inflation down the road.</detail><filename>808640newsML.xml</filename></pp></docs>