<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><docs><p0><title>USA: TABLE-TRM Copy Q4 shr profit before charge.</title><detail>TRM COPY CENTERS CORPORATION			   Consolidated Results of Operations			  (In thousands, except pershare data)			    Three Months Ended  Twelve Months Ended			   6-30-97     6-30-96   6-30-97    6-30-96 Sales		   $17,934     $17,701   $69,881    $67,538 Sales discounts	 2,978	 3,075    11,676     11,728 Net sales		14,956	14,626    58,205     55,810 Cost of sales	   7,656	 7,456    30,265     29,930 Gross profit	    7,300	 7,170    27,940     25,880Selling, general, &amp;amp;administrative expense			     4,556	 4,641    18,569     17,569Impairment of  long-lived assets    4,088	     0     4,088	    0 Operating income    (1,344)	 2,529     5,283	8,311 Interest expense	 (52)	 (178)     (396)	(957) Other expense, net    (330)	 (189)     (720)	(464)Income before  income taxes	 (1,726)	 2,162     4,167	6,890Provision for  income taxes	   (736)	   869     1,592	2,766 Net income		(990)	 1,293     2,575	4,124 Net income per share (0.13)	  0.18	0.35	 0.57 Shares outstanding    7,354	 7,340     7,337	7,262					Highlights					 Fiscal year ended 6-30-96			    Qtr. 1	Qtr. 2    Qtr. 3     Qtr. 4TRM Centers billed,  period end	    29,224	29,928    30,408     30,533Increase in TRM  Centers billed	   799	   704	 480	  125TRM Centers  installed, total     2,505	 2,269     2,216	2,529TRM Centers  removed, total	 1,526	 1,642     1,785	1,842TRM Centers  installed, net	   979	   627	 431	  687 Markets at period end    56	    58	  62	   66					 Fiscal year ended 6-30-97			    Qtr. 1	Qtr. 2    Qtr. 3     Qtr. 4TRM Centers billed,  period end	    32,574	32,965    33,647     34,638Increase in TRM  Centers billed	 2,041	   391	 682	  991TRM Centers  installed, total     2,391	 2,438     2,417	2,972TRM Centers  removed, total	 1,559	 2,233     1,688	1,661TRM Centers  installed, net	   832	   205	 729	1,311 Markets at period end    70	    71	  72	   72				TRM COPY CENTERS CORPORATION				Consolidated Balance Sheets				   (Dollars in Thousands)					Jun 30,		     Jun 30, Assets				 1997			   1996Current assets:  Cash and equivalents	   $2,528			  $873  Accounts receivable, net	7,704			 7,264  Inventories			 4,611			 5,253  Prepaid expenses and other    1,399			 1,580   Total current assets	  16,242			14,970 Equipment and vehicles, net   33,872			39,172 Other assets			    46			   109					 50,160			54,251Liabilities and Stockholders' EquityCurrent liabilities:  Checks in transit		 1,409			   938  Accounts payable		  1,568			 1,799  Accrued expenses		  3,697			 3,373   Total current liabilities    6,674			 6,110 Long-term debt			 400			 8,128 Deferred income taxes	    4,258			 4,569   Total liabilities	     11,332			18,807 Commitments			     --			    --Stockholders' equity:  Common stock		     16,601			16,214  Retained earnings		22,279			19,704Foreign currency   translation adjustment	  (52)			 (474)   Total stockholders' equity  38,828			35,444					 50,160			54,251NOTE: Net income per share for the fourth quarter was a record $0.21, against $0.18 a year ago, before a non-recurring charge relating to the application of a new accounting pronouncement.FULL CO NAME:  TRM Copy Centers Corp.-- New York Newsdesk 212 859-1610</detail><filename>809314newsML.xml</filename></p0><p1><title>GERMANY: Oil World sees higher Vietnamese oil/meal imports.</title><detail>Vietnamese import demand for vegetable oils and oilmeals in 1997/98 (Oct/Sept) should rise from an estimated 330,000 tonne combined total in 1996/97, the independent Oil World newsletter said.Drought was threatening the yield potential of domestic seed crops, it said.Domestic production of oilseed products would therefore not be able to keep pace with expanding demand, which was fuelled by Vietnam's strong economic growth.Annual per-capita consumption of oils and fats is currently only 4.5 kilos compared with a world average of 16.8 kilos.But local crushers were increasing their capacity to process more seeds on site in the years to come.The 1996/97 import total consists of 170,000 tonnes of oils and fats -- more than double the 1995/96 figure -- and 160,000 tonnes of oilmeals -- up from 95,000 tonnes in 1995/96.Palm oil is most prominent among oil imports and accounts for 110,000 tonnes out of the estimated 1996/97 total (84,000 tonnes in 1995/96), but the share of soy oil is rising.In meals, soymeal accounts for 148,000 tonnes out of the estimated 160,000 tonne import total in 1996/97.-Vera Eckert, Hamburg newsroom, +49-40-41903275</detail><filename>809829newsML.xml</filename></p1><p2><title>RUSSIA: Russian T-bill trade - 1.91 trln rbls transferred.</title><detail>Government securities dealers had transferred 1.91 trillion roubles to their government securities trading system accounts before the market opened on Tuesday, the central bank's open-market operations department said.Only money transferred to trading accounts before the market opens at 11 a.m. (0700 GMT) is available for investing in paper that day and is an indication of potential demand for GKO discount Treasury bills and OFZ interest-bearing government bonds.Average transfers are around two trillion roubles, though prices have risen recently despite much lower transfers.The total limit for short positions available to dealers licensed to conduct repo operations remains 2.00 trillion roubles. The rate for repos taken out on Monday, Tuesday and Wednesday remains 18 percent and for repos taken out on Thursday and Friday remains 21 percent. Repos taken out today will expire on August 21.Details of the last few days' transfers, and the central bank's net intervention in the market a week ago, can be seen on page  CBGKOINF.--Moscow Newsroom, +7095 941 8520e-mail: moscow.newsroom@reuters.com</detail><filename>808270newsML.xml</filename></p2><p3><title>INDIA: India Kodak 6-mth net at 41.1 mln rupees.</title><detail>Kodak India Ltd said on Tuesday it made a net profit of 41.1 million rupees in the first six months to June 30.Last year the company had changed its accounting period to calendar year and had drawn up accounts for the nine months to December 31, 1996.Net profit for the nine-month period was 47.4 million rupees, it said.  The net profit in the six month period to September 30 was 27.5 million rupees, the firm said in a statement.Net sales totalled 2.1 billion rupees in the latest period against 1.5 billion in the first half of previous year and other income was 13.5 million against 16.7 million.Expenditure took away 2.0 billion rupees against 1.4 billion and interest costs 21.6 million against 25.9 million, leaving a gross profit of 80.6 million in the six months to June 30 against 53.4 million in the first half of previous year.Allocations included 12 million rupees (10.9 million) for depreciation, 12.5 million (nil) for extraordinary item, and 15 million (same) for taxes.The extraordinary item represents a voluntary retirement scheme which has since been closed.The firm is 74 percent owned by the U.K. subsidiary of Eastman Kodak Company Ltd.--Bombay newsroom (91) 22-265-9000; Fax (91) 22-264-1699</detail><filename>809149newsML.xml</filename></p3><p4><title>CANADA: Newbridge Networks Q1 results.</title><detail>Newbridge Networks Corporation				  Statements of Earnings(Canadian dollars in thousands, except per share data)   Fiscal quarter August 3,		 July 27,						    1997		     1996						    ----		     ----    Sales				     $434,738		 $286,037    Cost of Sales			    160,730		  100,743						   -------		  -------    Gross Margin			     274,008		  185,294ExpensesSelling, general	  and administrative		 123,857		   66,258	Research and development	    59,683		   30,235						    ------		   ------    Income from operations		  90,468		   88,801    Other income				   553		    3,255						    ------		   ------Earnings before income taxes	and non-controlling interest	91,021		   92,056    Provision for income taxes	    27,034		   29,697    Non-controlling interest		  (367)		   1,558		   ------		    ------    Net earnings  $ 64,354		  $ 60,801						    ------		   ------						    ------		   ------Earnings per share	Cdn. GAAP - basic		   37 cents		  36cents	Cdn. GAAP - fully diluted	 34 cents		  35cents	U.S. GAAP - primary - US$	 26 cents		  25cents	U.S. GAAP - fully diluted - US$ 26 cents		  25cents				     Condensed Balance Sheets			    as at August 3, 1997 and April 30, 1997				  (Canadian dollars in thousands)						    August 3,	    April 30,							1997		   1997						     ------		 ------    Cash and cash equivalents	   $  353,961	    $333,904    Accounts receivable			413,686		387,338    Inventory				    191,495		159,495    Property, plant and equipment	  319,659		294,939    Goodwill				     121,102		125,565    Other assets				 179,961		195,462						   ---------	    ---------						  $1,579,864	   $1,496,703						   ---------	    ---------						   ---------	    ---------    Accounts payable and accruals     $  214,773	    $201,688    Restructuring reserve			7,240		 35,944    Income taxes				  45,902		 61,551    Long term obligations		     21,926		 18,170    Deferred taxes				28,546		 32,439    Non-controlling interest		  20,010		 20,412						   ---------	    ---------						     338,397		370,204    Shareholders' equity		   1,241,467	    1,126,499						   ---------	    ---------						  $1,579,864	   $1,496,703						   ---------	    ---------						   ---------	    ---------    -0-				 08/19/97/For further information: John Lawlor (613) 591-3600, johnlawlor(at)newbridge.com/</detail><filename>807599newsML.xml</filename></p4><p5><title>FRANCE: EdF said to pay more to French state.</title><detail>A re-organisation of the financial structure of state-electricity group Electricite de France (EdF), due to be discussed by the cabinet on Wednesday, will increase the amount of money the state can claim from the company each year.According to sector specialists, the 1996 payment by EdF would have been 5.6 billion francs ($905.8 million) instead of the four billion actually paid -- including a one-off social security payment of 2.5 billion.With a 1997 net income seen higher than the 5.9 billion francs of 1996, the state can look forward to a 1997 payment some three times more than the 1.5 billion it received for budget uses in 1996.The government on Thursday denied a report in the Financial Times that it wanted to recoup EdF's 30 billion francs in provisions or cream off its cash pile to square the 1998 budget, crucial for qualification for the euro.The government at the same time said it planned a reform of the ownership structure of assets used for the transport of energy, mainly the high-tension lines.EdF up to now leased the lines from the state but it will futurely own the lines. This transaction will be purely legal and there will be no payments made.The change was included in the &amp;quot;contract-plan&amp;quot; for 1997-2000 signed with the state in February.A result of this is that the group will get assets on its balance sheet and evolve towards a &amp;quot;normal&amp;quot; company status. It will be subject to normal corporate law and pay corporate taxes -- which were raised to 41.6 percent in July by the new Socialist-led government.Up to now, the state asked for contributions from EdF depending on its need for funds. The new contract-plan stipulates that the state, as owner, will get five percent of the capital injections up to 1997 and a dividend of 40 percent of the accounting profit.On top of that, the state will receive corporate tax.For the year 1996, this would have given 5.6 billion francs made up of five percent of 36 billion in capital injections, 40 percent of profit in dividend and 41.6 percent in corporate tax.In 1997, the profit will be higher than in 1996, partly due to debt reduction which cuts the financial charges.In 1996 these charges were already down by 32.2 percent compared to 1995.The accounting changes will allow EdF to keep its books in line with European directives related to the 1999 liberalisation of the European electricity market. The European Commission in particular wants a transparent accounting system showing the business of energy production separate from the transport of electricity.This is related to the fact that EdF will have to transport electricity to big users from the French border if a big user finds a European generator offering cheaper tariffs than EdF.-- William Emmanuel, Paris newsroom +33 1 4221 5452($ = 6.182 French Francs)</detail><filename>809787newsML.xml</filename></p5><p6><title>USA: Mar Ventures names Calerich CFO.</title><detail>Mar Ventures Inc said on Tuesday it has hired Andrew Calerich as the company's chief financial officer.Calerich worked as a consultant and controller from 1994 to 1997 at BWAB, a private oil and gas company in Denver, Mar Ventures said in a statement.&amp;quot;The hiring of a CFO will allow the management and technical staff of Mar Ventures to concentrate on the identification of significant exploration opportunities,&amp;quot; D. Scott Singdahlsen, president of Mar Ventures, said in a statement.Mar Ventures also announced the engagement of Wheeler Wasoff PC of Denver as its outside, independent accounting firm. Wheeler Wasoff, P.C. replaces Farber &amp;amp; Hass PC, which was the company's independent accounting firm before the purchase of PYR Energy LLC, Mar Ventures said.Earlier this month, Mar Ventures completed a private offering of $1.5 million net to the company. Concurrent with the offering it purchased a 100 percent interest in PYR Energy LLC in exchange for 4 million shares of common stock.Following the offering, the management of PYR Energy assumed the management of Mar Ventures. Plans are underway to seek shareholder approval to change the name of Mar Ventures to PYR Energy Corporation.</detail><filename>808671newsML.xml</filename></p6><p7><title>USA: TABLE - Gadzooks Q2 shr $0.02 vs $0.18.</title><detail>GADZOOKS, INC.STATEMENTS OF OPERATIONS(In thousands, except per share data)			   Second Quarter Ended    Six Months Ended			    Aug 2,	Jul 27,    Aug 2,   Jul 27,				1997	   1996	1997	1996 Net Sales	     $36,780	$28,504   $70,850   $51,990Cost of goods soldincluding buying,distribution and  occupancy costs     27,758	 19,634    51,701    36,173     Gross Profit	9,022	  8,870    19,149    15,817Selling, general andadministrative  expenses		 8,881	  6,423    17,114    12,409 Operating Income	  141	  2,447     2,O35     3,408 Interest income, net    134	    168	 376	 397Income before income  taxes			275	  2,615     2,411     3,805Provision for income  taxes			104	    968	 916     1,420 Net income		  171	  1,647     1,495     2,385Net income per commonand common equivalent  share		     0.02	   0.18	0.16	0.26Weighted average commonand common equivalent  shares outstanding   9,110	  9,116     9,118     9,074GADZOOKS, INC.CONDENSED BALANCE SHEETS(In thousands)					 Aug 2,			Feb 1,					   1997			  1997ASSETSCurrent assets:    Cash and cash equivalents  $7,017		     $10,348    Short-term investments     10,171			12,420    Accounts receivable	   3,275			 1,284    Inventory			30,713			23,211    Other current assets	  1,446			 1,328					 52,622			48,591Leaseholds, fixtures and equipment, net		21,496			16,156					 74,118			64,747LIABILITIES AND SHAREHOLDERS' EQUITYCurrent liabilities:    Accounts payable	     17,257			 7,654Accrued expenses &amp;amp;other current	liabilities		   4,002			 5,490    Income taxes payable	    386			 1,115					 21,645			14,259Accrued rent &amp;amp; other long-term obligations	    1,559			 1,425Shareholders' equity:    Common stock			 87			    86Additional paid-in     capital			 40,096			39,741    Retained earnings	    10,731			 9,236					 50,914			49,063					 74,118			64,747((-- New York Newsdesk 212 859-1610))</detail><filename>807664newsML.xml</filename></p7><p8><title>PAKISTAN: Pakistan telecom seen weathering cuts.</title><detail>Declining international accounting rates will have only a marginal impact on the revenue of state-run Pakistan Telecommunication Company Ltd (PTCL), a brokerage house research note said on Tuesday.ING Baring Securities said it would continue to recommend PTCL as a &amp;quot;core holding in a Pakistan portfolio&amp;quot; despite plans by the U.S. Federal Communications Commission (FCC) to force down accounting rates for international telephone calls.Accounting rates are used to determine how much telephone companies pay their counterparts in recipient countries for the cost of completing international calls.The United States has led calls for a global deal to slash international accounting rates. It unilaterally slashed 50 percent of its own international settlement fees in December and started negotiations with various telecom operators.Pakistan's settlement rates have not yet changed, but FCC Chairman Reed Hundt is reported to have said the FCC will cut settlement charges with all countries.Local newspapers on Monday said PTCL might implement periodic cuts in settlement charges with U.S. telephone companies after June 1998, which would hit its revenues.Those reports pushed PTCL's share price down 0.80 rupees to 38.10 rupees by 0745 GMT on Tuesday.Kalim Aziz, research head at ING Barings in Karachi, said the PTCL gets about 40 percent of its total revenue from net international settlement as it has a high incoming to outgoing ratio estimated at six to one.&amp;quot;To date, international telephony has been a steadily growing source of cashflow for the company which allowed it to fund its capital expenditure and keep domestic call rates at a very low level,&amp;quot; he said.ING Barings said PTCL's average net settlement rate per minute was likely to decline to $0.74 in 1999 and to $0.482 in 2002, from $1.193 in 1996. However, it said the expected decline in rates has been more than offset by an increase in line rent charges taking effect from July 1, 1997.PTCL last week announced that monthly line-rent had been increased to 125 rupees ($3.07) from 50 rupees and the one-time installation fee for a new connection to 4,150 rupees from 3,350. In June local call charges were raised 15 percent.ING Barings said PTCL should push ahead with rebalancing its domestic tariff structure, as it still has one of the lowest domestic call rates of $0.043 per call for unlimited duration.&amp;quot;This needs to be increased by at least 30 percent before it equates itself to its peer group per capita GDP (gross domestic product) countries,&amp;quot; the research note said.&amp;quot;It is more likely that the international operators (of developed markets) would reduce call rates more than PTCL. We expect this to lead to a higher increase in incoming call volume than the outgoing call volume, thus, improving the incoming to outgoing ratio in favour of PTCL,&amp;quot; it said.ING Barings said that given this marginal tariff rebalancing, its valuation of PTCL remained intact. At a discount of 25 percent for market risk, the value of PTCL's 10-rupee share should remain at 44 rupees, it added.</detail><filename>809163newsML.xml</filename></p8><p9><title>MALAYSIA: Malaysia PM threatens curbs on machinery imports.</title><detail>Malaysian Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad on Tuesday threatened fresh curbs on import of heavy, construction-related machinery in next year's annual budget to check a rising balance of payments deficit.&amp;quot;At the moment we want traders to voluntarily stop importing the machinery but if they don't, we are thinking of putting restrictions on the import,&amp;quot; the national Bernama news agency quoted Mahathir as saying in Kuching, capital of the Borneo state of Sarawak.He said import of heavy machinery such as cranes, excavators and bulldozers has contributed significantly to the country's balance of payments deficit.The government has this year imposed duties of five to 20 percent on heavy equipment to spur the development of the local construction machinery industry and control an increasing current account deficit.&amp;quot;The traders must realise that this deficit is a national problem and it will affect the traders themselves later on,&amp;quot; Mahathir told reporters after a two-day visit to Sarawak.When asked to elaborate on the type of restrictions the government was going to impose, Mahathir said he would have to consult the finance minister on the measures.Last week, Deputy Prime Minister and Finance Minister Anwar Ibrahim said the 1998 budget, to be tabled in Parliament in October, would look at measures to curb Malaysia's imports.&amp;quot;He (Mahathir) is certainly moving in the right direction. It means he is trying to reduce imports, but keep growth high,&amp;quot; said an analyst at another foreign brokerage in Kuala Lumpur.Mahathir has ignored suggestions for slowing down growth to let the fears of overheating in the economy subside. He has said Malaysia would reduce imports instead.The prime minister reiterated in Kuching that all projects would be carried out as planned.Some analysts said they would have to wait and see if these intentions are translated into action.&amp;quot;They (the government) have made several noises about curbing imports in the past. But I would not put too much validity in what has been said until we see some concrete action,&amp;quot; said an economist at a foreign research house.Anwar has said fiscal measures, including tax increases, would be used to increase exports and reduce imports.The two leaders' statements follow over a month of speculative selling of the ringgit, which has fallen 12 percent against the U.S. dollar.Malaysia has chalked up a trade deficit of 2.7 billion ringgit in the first six months of 1997 against 687.8 million ringgit deficit in the same perid last year.Many economists have expressed concern over the rising cost of imports for Malaysia and said that it was not yet out of the woods as far as its current account deficit problem was concerned.Markets had feared in 1995 that the economy was overheating after Malaysia reported a 9.5 percent gross domestic product (GDP) growth and current account deficit at over eight percent of the GDP.Malaysia responded by bringing down GDP growth to 8.2 percent and the deficit to five percent of GDP in 1996.Among listed companies likely to be adversely affected by the curbs would be UMW Holdings Bhd and Tractors Malaysia Holdings Bhd.A significant portion of their profits are derived from the import of heavy construction machinery, said analysts.United Bintang Bhd, however, could benefit as it specialises in reconditioning used machinery, they added.-- Kuala Lumpur Newsroom (603)201 4813; Fax (603)232 6752-- Email: kuala.lumpur.newsroom@reuters.com</detail><filename>808502newsML.xml</filename></p9></docs>